Let's welcome Bobby Jamison Travis
defensive lineman from Auburn your 186
pick of the sixth round in this draft.
BJT, can I call you BJT? I feel like I
know you already from what the two
minutes we've been on this Zoom call.
Yeah, you can call me BJT. Man, I bet
you ready to I bet you ready to take a
bite out of the Big Apple, man. So, come
on talk talk to me. What was it like
when you saw that 201 number pop up on
your phone?
Actually, I I was just sitting down um
really just being patient and waiting my
turn. And then I seen NY Giants
uh it popped up. I'm like, "Oh, snap."
I'm like,
I'm like I'm going to ask for that. Then
I got that call. I was very excited. All
right, man. Let's talk a little bit of
football here, man. You got drafted be
an anchor on this defensive line. I'm
sitting here looking at it. You anchored
an Auburn defensive line that ranked top
10 in rushing yards allowed. That's been
something that the Giants have struggled
at in recent years. Talk to me. How you
going to come in and you're going to
help fill that void and uh and stop the
run with the with the linebackers you
have behind you now.
Oh, yeah. Um shoot. Really 201 somebody
free.
And that's like always my mindset. I get
double-teamed in the trenches. Uh I know
a linebacker going to come in and fill.
So, I'm doing everything that's possible
to stop the run. Um really cuz I
consider myself as a run stopper.
>> Okay. And and I believe
it's my pride.
Was that what the line of the
conversations were like with you and the
Giants you know throughout the course of
this draft process? Kind of take us in
those rooms and those those Zoom calls
and those those conversations.
It was like like me and me and the
Giants like
we we locked in for sure. Like I had a
great time in my 30 visits there. Like I
connected with everybody in the rooms in
every room actually
with all the meetings we had. So, I had
a great connection with them. Um and it
really just a blessing to
for them to draft me.
I'm ready to go to work. Last but not
least, I'd like to ask the players
what's your why. We're talking about the
dog days, things aren't going right.
What's your why? What's that that that
reason or reasons that you wake up, you
show up to work, and you go 100% no
matter what?
Uh my why is really my mom and my
children. Uh my mom
you ready she had a lot of she had seven
kids and then adopted seven kids of her
own. And really she she's my why. Single
parent mama.
Um my dad passed away in 2013 from
natural cause. So, she really took in
that dad and mom role and she stood
strong and uh really made a way for us.
And then my kids you know they more
supportive than anything. Um they was at
all my games and all that ever since
they was born. So, really that's my why
my mom and my kids.
What's one thing in New York City you're
excited to do or to experience for the
first time?
>> Man, I ain't trying to experience
nothing. I'm ready to get to work.
>> That's what I'm talking about.
>> I'm ready to get to work.
>> [laughter]
>> Well, we can't wait to get you in the
building, man. That was a great answer
right there. I can't wait to get you in
the building. Congratulations. And uh
we'll we'll see you in a little bit,
bro.
Yes, sir.
>> [music]